HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series I. Faculty Photographs, 1908-2005
  - Subseries A. Faculty Photographs, A-Z, 1908-2005
    - Arch Shaw, circa 1920 (Box 24)
    - John Sheetz, 1960s (Box 24)
    - Alan P. Sheldon, 1970s (Box 24)
    - John J. Sherwood, 1970s (Box 24)
    - Gerald W. Siegel, circa 1960 (Box 24)
    - William W. Sihler, circa 1966 (Box 24)
    - Alvin J. Silk, 1990s (Box 24)
    - John B. Silvers, circa 1972 (Box 24)
    - William E. Simkin, circa 1970 (Box 24)
    - Robert L. Simons, 1980s (Box 24)
    - Erik R. Sirri, 1990s (Box 24)
    - Charles Wickham Skinner, 1966 (Box 24)
    - Charles Wickham Skinner, 1967 (Box 24)
    - Charles Wickham Skinner, 1970s (Box 24)
    - Charles Wickham Skinner, 1980s (Box 24)
    - Charles Wickham Skinner, 1990s (Box 24)
    - Allan P. Slaff, 1977 (Box 24)
    - Charles S. Sloane, circa 1992 (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, circa 1936 (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1940s (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1945-1946 (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1949 (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1960s (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Dan Throop Smith, 1981 (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith, 1935-1948 (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith, 1950s (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith- With Melvin T. Copeland, Frank Gilmore, Myles Mace, and Richard S. Meriam, circa 1955 (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith, 1955 (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith, circa 1960 (Box 24)
    - George Albert Smith, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Paul Solman, circa 1986 (Box 24)
    - Anthony M. Solomon, circa 1963 (Box 24)
    - Jeffrey A. Sonnenfeld, circa 1982 (Box 24)
    - Jeffrey A. Sonnenfeld, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Ralph Z. Sorenson, 1970s (Box 24)
    - Debora L. Spar, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Theresa C. Sparks, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Harold Spear, 1959 (Box 24)
    - Bert Spector, circa 1980 (Box 24)
    - Michael Spence, 1980s (Box 24)
    - Michael Spence, 1984 (Box 24)
    - W. Allen Spivey, circa 1960 (Box 24)
    - Oliver Wentworth Sprague, 1933 (Box 24)
    - Oliver Wentworth Sprague, 1939 (Box 24)
    - Oliver Wentworth Sprague- Clippings related to photographs, 1937-1941 (Box 24)
    - Robert T. Sprouse, circa 1963 (Box 24)
    - J. Owen Stalson, circa 1940 (Box 24)
    - Armstrong Stambaugh, 1948 (Box 24)
    - John Stamm, circa 1975 (Box 24)
    - Peter E.M. Standish, circa 1970 (Box 24)
    - Charles E. Staples, circa 1952 (Box 24)
    - Steven H. Star, 1970s (Box 24)
    - Laurence E. Steadman, circa 1980 (Box 25)
    - Charles Stein, Jr., circa 1959 (Box 25)
    - Jeremy C. Stein, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Louis W. Stern, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Jeremy Sternin, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Charles Leigh Stevens, circa 1953 (Box 25)
    - Howard H. Stevenson, 1977-1981 (Box 25)
    - Howard H. Stevenson, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Howard H. Stevenson, 1990s (Box 25)
    - Hebert F. Stewart, 1943 (Box 25)
    - Hebert F. Stewart, 1947-1949 (Box 25)
    - Hebert F. Stewart, 1950s (Box 25)
    - John B. Stewart, circa 1960 (Box 25)
    - Robert Stobaugh, circa 1968-1970 (Box 25)
    - Robert Stobaugh, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Robert Stobaugh, 1980s (Box 25)
    - Charles H. Stockton, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Donna Stoddard, 1990s (Box 25)
    - Lawrence Stone, circa 1980 (Box 25)
    - Richard E. Stone, circa 1982 (Box 25)
    - Harry W. Strachan, circa 1977 (Box 25)
    - Frederick D. Studivant, circa 1970 (Box 25)
    - John W. Sullivan, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Fareena Sultan, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Ralph G. Sultan, circa 1965-1970 (Box 25)
    - Bing Sung, circa 1971 (Box 25)
    - Barry E. Supple, circa 1956 (Box 25)
    - James R. Surface, 1949-1957 (Box 25)
    - Gerald Susman, circa 1993 (Box 25)
    - John J. Sviokla, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Carl F. Taeusch, 1932-1933 (Box 25)
    - Robert A. Taggart, Jr. circa 1993 (Box 25)
    - Renato Tagiuri, circa 1960 (Box 25)
    - Renato Tagiuri, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Renato Tagiuri, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Hirotaka Takeuchi, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Hirotaka Takeuchi, circa 1980 (Box 25)
    - Curtis W. Tarr, 1950 (Box 25)
    - Christopher S. Taylor, circa 1968 (Box 25)
    - Stuart Taylor, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Arthur Rothwell Tebbutt, circa 1932 (Box 25)
    - Richard Tedlow, circa 1979 (Box 25)
    - Richard Tedlow, circa 1985 (Box 25)
    - Richard Tedlow, circa 1990 (Box 25)
    - Richard Tedlow, circa 1992 (Box 25)
    - Richard Tedlow, circa 1995 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1930s (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, circa 1945 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1949 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1950s (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Portraits, circa 1950 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, circa 1955 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- With George P. Baker, circa 1955 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Portrait, 1955 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- On cover of Business Week, 25 June 1955 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- At desk, circa 1956 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- With Vice-President Richard Nixon, circa 1958 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- At staff meeting, circa 1958 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1958 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- With secretary, 1958 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- On cover of Management Methods, June 1959 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1960s (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- In academic robe, 1960s (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Photographs by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1960 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1960, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Teaching, circa 1960 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele, 1960 (Box 25)
    - Stanley F. Teele- Presenting first National City Bank of Cleveland Fellowship, 1961 (Box 25)
    - Elizabeth Teisberg, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Michael L. Tennican, circa 1967 (Box 25)
    - Irwin Tepper, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Dan R. E. Thomas, circa 1976 (Box 25)
    - David A. Thomas, 1990s (Box 25)
    - Roosevelt Thomas, Jr., circa 1974 (Box 25)
    - Stuart Denis Thomas, circa 1967 (Box 25)
    - Lawrence E. Thompson, circa 1953 (Box 25)
    - Lawrence E. Thompson, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Paul H. Thompson, circa 1971 (Box 25)
    - Eric Thor, circa 1965 (Box 25)
    - Harold Hazen Thurlby, 1932 (Box 26)
    - Philip H. Thurston, circa 1960-1990 (Box 26)
    - George C. Tiao, circa 1966 (Box 26)
    - Seymour Tilles, circa 1961 (Box 26)
    - C. Peter Timmer, circa 1981 (Box 26)
    - Jeffry A. Timmons, circa 1989 (Box 26)
    - Barbara Toffler, circa 1981 (Box 26)
    - Steven Tolliday, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal, 1935-1937 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal, 1949 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal, circa 1950 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal- Teaching, 1954 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal- At desk, 1956 (Box 26)
    - Harry R. Tosdal- Teaching AMP class, 1956 (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl, 1940s (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl- Teaching, 1946 (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl, 1948 (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl- With Melvin T. Copeland and Mr. Houghton, circa 1950 (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl- With Grace Lindfors and Charles N. Gebhard, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Andrew Towl, circa 1985 (Box 26)
    - Robert Traupe, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Eoin W. Trevelyan, circa 1973 (Box 26)
    - Yoshihior Tsurumi, circa 1973 (Box 26)
    - Frank L. Tucker, 1970s (Box 26)
    - Peter Tufano, circa 1985 (Box 26)
    - Arthur H. Tully- With Melvin T. Copeland, circa 1947 (Box 26)
    - Arthur H. Tully, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Arthur N. Turner, 1949 (Box 26)
    - Arthur N. Turner, 1980s (Box 26)
    - Glen Corbin Turner, 1937 (Box 26)
    - Earl Wayne Tyler, circa 1943 (Box 26)
    - Marcie J. Tyre, circa 1983 (Box 26)
    - Israel Unterman, 1968 (Box 26)
    - William L. Ury, circa 1983 (Box 26)
    - James M. Utterback, circa 1976 (Box 26)
    - Hugo E.R. Uyterhoeven, circa 1961 (Box 26)
    - Hugo E.R. Uyterhoeven- Teaching, 1970s (Box 26)
    - Hugo E.R. Uyterhoeven, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Hugo E.R. Uyterhoeven, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Hugo E.R. Uyterhoeven, 1990s (Box 26)
    - Detlev F. Vagts, circa 1976 (Box 26)
    - Peter Vail, circa 1960 (Box 26)
    - Richard F. Vancil, circa 1970 (Box 26)
    - Richard F. Vancil, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Richard F. Vancil, circa 1985 (Box 26)
    - Bart J. Van Dissell, circa 1986 (Box 26)
    - Harold B. van Gorder, circa 1963 (Box 26)
    - Harold B. van Gorder, 1970s (Box 26)
    - John R. Van Slyke, circa 1983 (Box 26)
    - John R. Van Slyke, circa 1984 (Box 26)
    - Walter H. Vandaele, circa 1976 (Box 26)
    - Robert F. Vandell, circa 1957 (Box 26)
    - Homer Vanderblue, 1950 (Box 26)
    - Paul A. Vatter, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Paul A. Vatter-Teaching, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Raymond Vernon, circa 1961 (Box 26)
    - Raymond Vernon, 1970 (Box 26)
    - Raymond Vernon, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Richard H.K. Vietor, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Peter C.M.S. von Braun, circa 1970 (Box 26)
    - Michael Von Clemm, 1971 (Box 26)
    - George A. von Peterffy- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1971 (Box 26)
    - John H. Vogel, Jr., circa 1994 (Box 26)
    - Pierre Wack, circa 1984 (Box 26)
    - Harvey M. Wagner, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker, 1937-1948 (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker, 1951-1956 (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker- Group photographs, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1960 (Box 26)
    - Ross G. Walker- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1960, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Kelvin A. Wall, circa 1970 (Box 26)
    - James E. Walter, circa 1959 (Box 26)
    - Richard E. Walton, 1960s (Box 26)
    - Richard E. Walton, circa 1980 (Box 26)
    - Lewis B. Ward, 1948-1950s (Box 26)
    - Lewis B. Ward, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Lewis B. Ward, circa 1990 (Box 26)
    - Scott Ward, 1970s (Box 26)
    - Scott Ward, circa 1978 (Box 26)
    - Nancy N. Wardell, circa 1974 (Box 26)
    - Nancy N. Wardell- Teaching, circa 1975 (Box 26)
    - James P. Ware, circa 1977 (Box 27)
    - William Lloyd Warner, circa 1934 (Box 27)
    - Frank D. Washburn, 1929 (Box 27)
    - Frederick E. Webster, circa 1988 (Box 27)
    - Mary M. Wehle, circa 1972-1973 (Box 27)
    - Ronald Lee Weiher, 1970s (Box 27)
    - Martha Weinberg, circa 1984 (Box 27)
    - Martha Weinberg, circa 1985 (Box 27)
    - Matthew Weisman, circa 1985 (Box 27)
    - John W. Welcker, 1946-1948 (Box 27)
    - Philip A. Wellons, circa 1976 (Box 27)
    - Philip A. Wellons, 1980s (Box 27)
    - Philip A. Wellons- Teaching, 1980s (Box 27)
    - Philip A. Wellons, 1982 (Box 27)
    - Philip A. Wellons, 1987 (Box 27)
    - John R. Wells, circa 1982 (Box 27)
    - Louis T. Wells, Jr., 1960s (Box 27)
    - Gerald O. Wentworth, circa 1962 (Box 27)
    - John Philip Wernette, 1934-1939 (Box 27)
    - Samuel Z. Westerfield, circa 1950 (Box 27)
    - Frank Weston, circa 1960 (Box 27)
    - Guy Weyns, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Steven C. Wheelwright, circa 1972 (Box 27)
    - William B. Whiston, circa 1968 (Box 27)
    - Donald White, circa 1976 (Box 27)
    - George R. White, 1970s (Box 27)
    - Gerald T. White, circa 1953 (Box 27)
    - William L. White, 1960s (Box 27)
    - William L. White, 1970 (Box 27)
    - William L. White- With Jay Light, circa 1975 (Box 27)
    - William L. White, 1977 (Box 27)
    - Thomas North Whitehead, 1940s (Box 27)
    - Howard Whitmore, circa 1973 (Box 27)
    - John C. Whitney, circa 1984 (Box 27)
    - John O. Whitney, circa 1968 (Box 27)
    - John O. Whitney, 1970 (Box 27)
    - Clay Whybark, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Ulrich E. Wiechmann, circa 1973 (Box 27)
    - Ulrich E. Wiechmann- Teaching, circa 1975 (Box 27)
    - Bruce Wilburn, 1971 (Box 27)
    - William Wilkie, 1973 (Box 27)
    - Florence Wilkins, 1978 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams, 1948 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams, 1950s (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams- Portraits, circa 1957 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams- Teaching, 1960s (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams, circa 1965 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams- Teaching, 1965 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams- Teaching, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams, 1970s-1980s (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams, 1979 (Box 27)
    - Charles M.Williams- At alumni event, 1984 (Box 27)
    - J. Peter Williamson, circa 1959 (Box 28)
    - Peter J. Williamson, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Rodney Willoghby, 1948 (Box 28)
    - Clark L. Wilson, circa 1965 (Box 28)
    - G. Peter Wilson, circa 1988 (Box 28)
    - Milton Wilson, circa 1958 (Box 28)
    - Rudolph Winston, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Ronald F. Wippern, circa 1973 (Box 28)
    - Charles C. Withers, circa 1958 (Box 28)
    - Charles C. Withers, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Mark A. Wolfson, circa 1989 (Box 28)
    - David Wood, circa 1970 (Box 28)
    - Donald H. Woods, circa 1967 (Box 28)
    - Arthur Vernon Woodworth, 1935 (Box 28)
    - Thomas K. Worthington, 1971 (Box 28)
    - H. Edward Wrapp- With Robert W. Merry and Herbert F. Stewart, circa 1956 (Box 28)
    - H. Edward Wrapp- Portraits, circa 1956 (Box 28)
    - Karen Hopper Wruck, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Karen Hopper Wruck, 1990s (Box 28)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff- Teaching, 1970s (Box 28)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff, circa 1970 (Box 28)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff- Group photograph taken in China, circa 1970, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff, circa 1972 (Box 28)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff- Driving a truck, circa 1975 (Box 28)
    - D. Daryl Wyckoff, circa 1980 (Box 28)
    - Harold E. Wyman, circa 1965 (Box 28)
    - Irma Wyman, 1993 (Box 28)
    - John Yeager, 1960s (Box 28)
    - Daniel Yergin, 1977 (Box 28)
    - George S. Yip, circa 1981 (Box 28)
    - David B. Yoffie, 1980s (Box 28)
    - Michael Y. Yoshino, 1970s (Box 28)
    - Michael Y. Yoshino, circa 2000 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, circa 1949 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- With C. Roland Christensen at prediction study site, 1955 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, 1960 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- Teaching, 1960 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, 1966 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, 1978 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, 1980s (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- Teaching, 1980s (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- Book jackets, 1980s (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- In faculty office, circa 1985 (Box 28)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Abraham Zaleznik- Teaching, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Abraham Zaleznik, circa 1986 (Box 28)
    - William M. Zani, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Stephen A. Zeff, circa 1972 (Box 28)
    - Edwin V. Zschau, circa 1967 (Box 28)
    - Eugene Martin Zuckert, circa 1940 (Box 28)
  - Subseries B. Group Faculty Photographs, 1940s-circa 1990
    This subseries consists of photographs of groups of faculty, some posed on steps, many at meetings in various places on campus. Included are casual photographs of faculty playing poker, at dinners, or attending other social events. This subseries includes general group photographs and also group photographs organized by teaching department. Faculty members represented include Malcolm P. McNair, Stanley F. Teele, Donald K. David, among many others.
    - Groups, 1940s (Box 29)
    - Groups- Faculty Club at Morgan Hall, 1949 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1950s (Box 29)
    - Groups- Case discussions, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Groups- Poker game, circa 1965 (Box 29)
      Photographs of faculty poker game, including Malcolm P. McNair at poker table.
    - Groups, 1970s (Box 29)
    - Groups- At Museum of Science, circa 1970 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Groups- Faculty Club at Kresge, circa 1975 (Box 29)
    - Groups- Rowing on Charles River, circa 1975 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1975 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Groups, 1980s (Box 29)
    - Group, circa 1980, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Groups, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Group, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Groups, circa 1990 (Box 29)
    - Accounting and Control- Clarence B. Nickerson, Ross G. Walker, and Windsor A. Hosmer, circa 1950 (Box 29)
    - Accounting and Control- Charles A. Bliss, Robert O. Schlaifer, Arthur Hanson, and William Jerome, circa 1953 (Box 29)
    - Advanced Management Program, 1954 (Box 29)
    - Business Administration, 1949 (Box 29)
    - Business Administration, 1950s (Box 29)
    - Business Administration- Case report writing, circa 1950 (Box 29)
    - Business Administration, 1953 (Box 29)
    - Finance, 1950s (Box 29)
    - Finance, 1965 (Box 29)
    - Human Relations, 1940s (Box 29)
    - Human Relations, 1950s (Box 29)
    - Marketing, circa 1950 (Box 29)
    - Marketing, 1970s-1980s (Box 29)
    - Organizational Behavior- Steven Fuller, Ben A. Lindberg, and James Healy, circa 1950 (Box 29)
    - Trade Union Program, 1954 (Box 29)
    - Headshots, Boaz-Zaleznik, 1940s (Box 29)
      Contains small headshots of faculty mounted onto sheets of paper in alphabetical order.
  - Subseries C. Unidentified Faculty, circa 1940-circa 2000
    This subseries consists of various individual unidentified faculty members. Includes portraits, and photographs of faculty teaching in the classroom, in offices and on campus.
    - Unidentified, circa 1940 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 10 April 1945 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 8 October 1947 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1950s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 1960s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1960s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1960 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1965 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- On cover of Purchasing magazine, 12 June 1969 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 1970s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1970s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1970 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1977 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 1980s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1980s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, 1980s, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Unidentified, circa 1980 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Teaching, circa 1980 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1983 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1985 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Unidentified, 1990s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1990 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 1995 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified, circa 2000 (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Contact sheets, 1960s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Contact sheets, 1970s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Contact sheets, 1970s-1980s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Contact sheets, 1980s (Box 30)
    - Unidentified- Contact sheets, 1990s (Box 30)
- Series II. Staff Photographs, 1940-2001
  This series consists of photographs of HBS staff and includes portraits, photographs of staff working in offices, and staff socializing. The series has been arranged into three subseries: an alphabetical list of staff members, unidentified staff members, and group photographs of HBS departments.
  - Subseries A. Staff, A-Z, circa 1940-circa 1994
    This subseries consists of individual HBS staff members arranged alphabetically. When possible, department affiliation has been identified as well as research assistants and research associates. Note that research associates and assistants were often MBA graduates and doctoral candidates.
    - Laurence J. Ackerman, circa 1956 (Box 31)
    - Titus O. Adeboye (Research Assistant), 1975 (Box 31)
    - James E. Aisner (Marketing and Communications), circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Paula Alexander, circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Carl F. Allen, Jr. (MBA Admissions), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - Carol Allen (Administrative Services), circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Laurance Allen (Harvard Business Review), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Marjorie Allen (Senior Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Elizabeth Altman (Research Associate), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Alice Amsden, February 1984 (Box 31)
    - Manuela Andrews (MBA Admissions), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Barbara Ankeny (Division of Research), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Edward Anthony (HBS Bulletin), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Gordon R. Antleman (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - James Armour (Research Associate), 1950s (Box 31)
    - Robert M. Armstrong (Alumni Services), 1991 (Box 31)
    - Anthony Artuso (HBS Publishing), 1989 (Box 31)
    - Mary Beth Avedesian (Department of Operations), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Margaret C. Auerdahl (Alumni Placement), 1940s-1960s (Box 31)
    - Jo Anne M. Austad, circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Bernard Avishai (Harvard Business Review), 1987 (Box 31)
    - Robert C. Aylmer, Jr., 1970s (Box 31)
    - Frank C. Ayres, circa 1935 (Box 31)
    - George L. Baker (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - Michael Baldwin (Research Associate), 1988 (Box 31)
    - Richard Ballau, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Pamela M. Banks (Harvard Business Review), circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Jeffrey A. Barach (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - Sandy Barke, ca. 1980 (Box 31)
    - Ben Baron (MBA Admissions), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Audrey Barrett (HBS Publishing), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - James F. Bateman (Research Assistant), Jr., circa 1945 (Box 31)
    - Peter Bauer, circa 1975 (Box 31)
    - Linda D. Baydin (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 31)
    - David Bayer (Baker Library), circa 1995 (Box 31)
    - George Beal (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - James D. Berkley (Research Associate), 1991-1993 (Box 31)
    - Katherine F. Beaver (Baker Library), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Miss Bell (Case Distribution), circa 1960 (Box 31)
    - Izak Benbasat, circa 1975 (Box 31)
    - Cathy M. Bennigson (Office of Student Affairs), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Blair A. Bergstrom (Harvard Business Review, circa 1980) (Box 31)
    - Deborah Bernton, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Kurt Billick (Research Associate), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Kathryn Bing-You (HBS Bulletin), circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Deb Blagg, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Michael Blair, circa 1980, (Contact sheets) (Box 31)
    - Jean F. Blodgett, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Timothy B. Blodgett (Harvard Business Review), circa 1960-1979 (Box 31)
    - Daniel Bloomfield (Visiting Consultant), circa 1961 (Box 31)
    - Marc W. Boatwright (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Doris E. Bogues, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Harry M. Boon, Jr., circa 1960 (Box 31)
    - Neil H. Borden (Research Associate), Jr., circa 1958 (Box 31)
    - Baldwin James Borreson (MBA Admissions), 1950s (Box 31)
    - Stephen M. Boucher (HBS Publishing), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Jane W. Bowen, circa 1975 (Box 31)
    - Ms. Bowers, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Donald S. Bradshaw (Research Associate), circa 1953 (Box 31)
    - Monica L. Brand (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Harold F. Braudis, circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - Lillian Braudis, circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Margaret C. Britton (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - George Brown (Department of Operations), 1990 (Box 31)
    - Julian Z. Brown (Research Assistant), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - David D Brunell (Office of the Dean), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Kent Bullock, circa 1980, (Contact sheets) (Box 31)
    - Richard W. Burack (Health Services), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Jean Burleson (Case Services), 1970s (Box 31)
    - Monique A. Burnett (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Tim Butler (MBA Counseling Services), circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Fleur Byers, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Mark L. Byers, circa 1975 (Box 31)
    - Carol A. Cahill (Baker Library), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Elizabeth M. Cahill, circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Andrew P. Cahners (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Tom Cameron (HBS Publishing), circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Mark D. Cannon (Research Associate), circa 1998 (Box 31)
    - Peter Capodilupo, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Diane Carlson (Executive Education), 1990 (Box 31)
    - Barryn Carlton, circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Kenneth E. Carpenter (Baker Library), circa 1965-circa 1970 (Box 31)